

PROFILE

I'm Mehmet, originally from Turkey and currently residing in Switzerland with a **B** residence permit. I am a passionate and skilled Full Stack Developer with a strong focus on **Next.js**, **React.js**, **Angular**, **Node.js**, **Nest.js**, **Docker**, **Playwright**, and **Kubernetes**. As a Web Developer with **18** months of experience able to build web applications from the ground up - information gathering, planning, design, development, testing and delivery, and maintenance.

CONTACT

PHONE:

+41 772590414

GitHub:

https://aithub.com/sayinmehmet47

EMAIL:

sayinmehmet47@gmail.com

LINKEDIN

linkedin.com/in/sayinmehmet

LANGUAGE

Turkish-Mother Tongue

English-C1
Arabic-C1

German-B1 (Still continue to course)

CERTIFICATION

- FreeCodeCamp: JavaScript Algoritm and Data Structures
- ☐ FreeCodeCamp: Responsive Web
 Design
- Backend Development and APIs
- Frontend Web Development Course
- ☐ Microservices with Node JS and React

MEHMET SAYIN

Full Stack Web Developer

WORK EXPERIENCE

Steiner AG - Junior Full Stack Developer

10/2022 - Still working here

I have contributed to the development of Collab Room, a robust and user-friendly application that meets the construction industry's project management needs. I have worked closely with a cross-functional team to build the application using technologies like **Nx Monorepo**, **NestJS**, **Tailwind CSS**, **Next.js**, **and PostgreSQL**. Additionally, I have used Playwright to develop and maintain end-to-end tests to ensure the scalability and quality of the application.

Roambee-Junior Full Stack Developer

05/2022-09/2022

Worked with Single SPA, Monorepo, NestJS, Graphql, SCSS, NextJS, PostgreSQL, Docker Writing some E2E test with Cypress

My working time was short since Zurich office was closed

XYZ Reality - Frontend Developer

06/2021 - 09/2021

Building user interfaces for websites and/or web applications Working with ReactJS, Redux, NodeJS, MongoDB, TypeScript Creating self-contained, reusable, and testable modules and components

Writing some end-to-end test on Cypress, JestJS

EDUCATION

Turkish Military Academy - Ankara

2009 - 2013

Bachelor of Science: Industrial and Systems Engineering - 3.20/4.00

Social Hackers Academy - Athens

03/2021 - 11/2021

Learned Html, Sass, CSS, JS, ReactJS, NextJS, Redux, NodeJS, TypeScript, Strapi. Firebase, MongoDB, TypeOrm, PostgreSQL, Docker